

# Bernard Tshabu Ngandu

# **Web Developer**

Je rêve d'acquérir la liberté d'aider les gens par le truchement de nouveaux produits, de les aider à grandir par l'expérience et à réaliser leurs rêves et leur indépendance. Pour moi, le développement de logiciels est une forme d'expression, je ne peux pas davantage convenir que le développement de logiciels est un art

ngandubernard@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Lac Kipopo 10465, Kalubwe, Lubum bashi, Haut-Katanga, RD Congo

#### **Phone**

0892530482

Date of birth

07-23-2000

**Nationality** 

Congolese

Link

linkedin.com/in/bernard-ngandu/? \_l=en\_US

# Experience

Lubumbashi, RD Congo October 2020 - April 2021 Lead Web Developer

#### **Itotafrica**

Development of custom web solutions for Itotafrica and its clients, maintenance and project design

Brussels, Belgium June 2020 - September 2020 Lead Web Developer

#### **Eshima Software**

Project management and implementation of backend architecture for the eshima structure based in Belgium

Amsterdam, Netherlands January 2019 - July 2020 **Backend Developer** 

#### **Goodbytes**

Development of XMPP server management application and redesign of victrine goodbytes.nl website

Lubumbashi, RD Congo March 2019 - March 2019 **Accounting Assistant** 

#### Office Congolais de Contrôle

Humanitarian end-of-study internship in the commercial and management section

### Skills



# Languages

#### **Français**

Advanced

# **Anglais**

Intermediate. Diplôme d'Anglais Lusaka

#### Shwahili

Advanced

# Education

Lubumbashi, RD Congo September 2015 - September 2019 Commercial and Management

## C.S Imani / Mgr Nsolotshy

State Diploma in Commercial Management

Lubumbashi, RD Congo

**Hacking Computer Ethics** 

Agence Universitaire de la Francopnonie August 2019 - August 2019 Hacking training for computer systems security diploma 1079F0B6.1.1-018 Software Development Lubumbashi, RD Congo 2017 - 2020 Udemy

training in software development and other related fields